<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="string_array_banners">
        <item>img_btn_about_us</item>
        <item>img_btn_our_people</item>
        <item>img_btn_outreach</item>
        <item>img_btn_research</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="string_array_titles">
        <item>50 years of world-class, future-focused education and research</item>
        <item>Our staff</item>
        <item>Outreach activities</item>
        <item>Research from School of Computing and Mathematical Sciences</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="string_array_content">
        <item>At the School of Computing and Mathematical Sciences, there are many exciting opportunities and possibilities here. We strive to inspire and challenge our students so they emerge qualified and ready for a successful and fulfilling career. \n\n Our School is the first New Zealand member of the international group of iSchools - a partnership of the world\'s leading information schools. \n\n World-class researchers and facilities underpin unique collaborations within our School, across campus, and with the wider world. These collaborations bring together creative minds, unique technologies, and degree structures tailored to your interests and skills. \n\n We offer three and four-year degree undergraduate programmes that are based on a strong foundation in the computing and mathematical sciences. \n\n A qualification in Computer Science, Mathematics, Data Analytics, Software Engineering or Design can open many doors, and our former students - both in New Zealand and overseas - are using their training to make a positive contribution to the world we live in. We are always updating our papers and qualifications to ensure they are relevant in the world\'s rapidly changing technological and social environment. \n\n If you\'re thinking about studying with us, we\'d love to chat about the best programme of study for you. If you\'re enrolled and ready to start, a warm welcome on behalf of our team. We look forward to seeing you complete your studies and going on to achieve a fulfilling career.</item>
        <item>Computer Science and Software Engineering:\n\n - Professor Annika Hinze\n    Head of Computing and Mathematical Sciences\n - Professor Bernhard Pfahringer\n    Professor, Co-Director AI Institute\n - Professor David Bainbridge\n    Programme Lead, Information Technology\n - Professor Eibe Frank\n    Professor, Co-Director\n - Professor Geoffrey Holmes\n    Pro Vice-Chancellor HECS\n - Professor Mark Apperley\n    Professor, Research Associate\n - Professor Steve Reeves\n    Professor\n - Associate Professor David Nichols\n    Associate Professor\n - Associate Professor Judy Bowen\n    Associate Dean Academic, Associate Professor\n - Associate Professor Sally Jo Cunningham\n    Associate Professor\n - Associate Professor Te Taka Keegan\n    Co-Director Māori, Associate Professor\n - Dr Alvin Yeo\n    Developer AGS\n - Dr Cameron Grout\n    Teaching Fellow\n - Dr Colin Pilbrow\n    Teaching Fellow\n - Dr Farzana Zahid\n    Lecturer\n - Dr Jemma Konig\n    Lecturer\n - Dr Jessica Turner\n    Lecturer, Programme Lead\n - Dr Junaid Haseeb\n    Lecturer\n - Dr Marinho Barcellos\n    Senior Lecturer, Programme Lead\n - Dr Nandana Peramuna Pathirage\n    Teaching Fellow\n - Dr Sapna Jaidka\n    Teaching Fellow\n - Dr Shaoqun Wu\n    Research Associate\n - Dr Tony Smith\n    Senior Lecturer\n - Dr Vimal Kumar\n    Research Associate\n - Mr Aaron Matenga\n    Lecturer\n - Mr Dale Fletcher\n    Senior Research Manager\n - Mr Nilesh Kanji\n    Senior Tutor\n - Mr Peter Reutemann\n    Senior Research Programmer\n - Mr Phillip Treweek\n    Senior Tutor\n - Mr Tim Elphick\n    Head Tutor\n - Mrs Harpreet Kaur\n    Research Programmer\n - Mrs Katherine Don\n    Senior Research Programmer\n - Ms Anupama Krishnan\n    Research Programmer\n\nDesign:\n\n - Dr Claire Timpany\n    Head of Design\n - Dr Nicholas Vanderschantz\n    Senior Lecturer, Programme Lead\n - Dr Pierre Lubis\n    Teaching Fellow\n - Mr Keith Soo\n    Senior Lecturer\n - Mr Rowan Simmons\n    Tutor\n - Mr Tomás García Ferrari\n    Senior Lecturer\n - Ms Carolina Short\n    Lecturer\n\nMathematics and Data Analytics:\n\n - Professor Sean Oughton\n    Professor, Programme Lead\n - Associate Professor Jacob Heerikhuisen\n    Deputy Head of School, Associate Professor\n - Associate Professor Nicholas Cavenagh\n    Associate Professor\n - Dr Han Gan\n    Programme Leader Data Analytics Group\n - Dr Ian Hawthorn\n    Senior Lecturer\n - Dr Jason Kurz\n    Lecturer\n - Dr Paul Brown\n    Senior Lecturer\n - Dr Raziyeh Zarre\n    Teaching Fellow\n - Dr Sampath Fernando\n    Teaching Fellow\n - Dr Tim Stokes\n    Programme Lead, Mathematics\n - Dr Woei Chet Lim\n    Teaching Fellow\n\nAdministrative Staff:\n\n - Mrs Carol Home\n    School Manager - CMS\n - Mrs Maria Admiraal\n    School Administrator\n - Mrs Bronwyn Webster\n    Research Administrator\n</item>
        <item>Are you looking for ways to inspire your students and show them the exciting possibilities that lie ahead in the fields of computing, data analytics, design, and mathematics? \n\nOur free outreach programmes offer hands-on experiences and engaging activities that will allow your students to explore these fields in a fun and interactive way. By participating in our outreach programmes, your students will not only gain valuable skills and knowledge but also be motivated to pursue further education and careers in these exciting fields. Sign up today - and help your students unlock their full potential.</item>
        <item>Research activities in the School of Computing and Mathematical Sciences take place in research centres and groups. Although many staff participate in projects across different groups, we have arranged the descriptions into these areas, but understand that in practice there is considerable overlap between the activities in the various groups.\n\nResearch Groups:\n - Cyber Security Research Group\n - Design Research Group\n - Digital Library Research Group\n - Energy Informatics Group\n - Formal Methods Group\n - Human-Computer Interaction Group\n - Information Systems And Databases Group\n - Machine Learning Group\n - Mathematics Research Group</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>